497 498 499 500 Let's go heavy Yeah got it Looking strong
Nick Red one is on the move Evening ladies What are you
so excited about Of course your boyfriend's here OK Who's with Red
Reach Someone took Nick We're gonna find him I'm bringing in Jack
O'Malley He's probably the best tracker in the world The guy's a
legend What am I doing here Last night Red One also known
as Saint Nicholas of Myra was abducted from the North Pole complex
Are you saying Santa Claus has been kidnapped Garcia What the hell
You can't trust this guy He's on the list You don't mean
Yes that list NL4 Are you telling me this clown is a
level 4 naughty lister a level 4 naughty lister Oh is that
funny to you Hey hey hey you're gonna help us find Nick
Come on let's go Grab a car for what You don't have
a Wonder Woman action figure do you It's not how it works
Come on There is much in here that is not of the
natural world Who's that Krampus What are they doing They're playing rapper
slop I think if you don't need me here I might just
go back to the car We need to prepare for the possibility
of no Christmas There's worse ways to go out than trying to
save Santa Claus We got snowmen Whatever That was so disturbing Hm
interesting My turn Oh my God Is my face still there Yeah
yeah you look Good